Excuse me, sir.
Yeah, what's up?
Question for you.
Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yeah.
And what do you do for living out here
in Tampa to be able to afford a Rolls Royce?
I am a consultant.
How long have you been a business owner for?
I've been a business owner for 37, no, 39 years.
And can I interview you real quick?
Sure.
I go all over the country just
asking business owners advice to new entrepreneurs.
Sure.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Man, I'm not going to say.
Over $10 million?
Over, yeah.
It's going to be my current year.
I'm making a few million this year, bro.
Yeah.
Give me a range.
$45 million.
Yeah.
Most amount of money I've ever
made in a single year, $15 million.
Have you ever been broke before?
Oh, God, yeah.
I literally walked into a bank on Saturday
and met with the president of the bank on
the day he was off and got a
loan for $550,000 and opened my first business.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No.
I grew up on a farm.
In 60 seconds, how can somebody
become a multimillionaire in today's world?
We just landed in one of the
wealthiest cities in the entire country, Tampa, Florida.
And for those that don't know, Tampa, Florida.
It's home to over 60,000
millionaires and nearly 10 billionaires.
And we're going to be going all over
the city to the wealthiest areas to ask multimillionaires
and people that have grown some of the
biggest companies in the entire city how they became
successful and how you can start your
path to becoming financially free in today's world.
So with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Yes.
Have you ever owned a business before?
What type of company?
Several.
What was your main business?
I was in the TV business.
I was in the restaurant business.
Let me ask you a question.
I started the channel on Austin.
Million followers.
I go all over the country just asking
business owners their best advice to new entrepreneurs.
Could I get one minute of your time real quick?
Real quick.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
My whole life.
What's the greatest lesson
you learned about entrepreneurship?
A lesson you learned that somebody will not learn.
Take care of your people.
And the worst thing you can have is
have a big corporation take over the company and
try and homogenize everything.
It doesn't work because they don't care about the staff.
You take care of your
people, you're going to be successful.
Is that what happened to you?
Yeah, they bought us out.
I made great money, but in terms of revenue,
what was the most amount of money that you
made in a single year?
TV stations.
We're doing 30, 40 million.
The restaurant was doing 5 million.
Did you ever lose money?
Oh God, yeah.
I had businesses that didn't work.
I always tried to have three sources
of income, three different businesses in different categories
working to make money.
But a lot of people would say, don't diversify.
How do you feel about that?
They're wrong because you don't want to have
the old classic, don't put all your eggs in
one basket.
I was in the restaurant business.
I was in the farming business
and I was in the television business.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No, I grew up on a farm.
Yeah.
So what was the turning point to financial freedom?
What did you see that made you want to
go out and build a big million dollar business?
Well, my dad was a farmer.
He took a risk every day.
How old are you now?
I'm almost 70.
No, you're not.
Are you actually?
I'll be 70 next year.
Are you serious?
Real quick, real quick.
Come here.
If you lost everything tomorrow,
could you make it all back?
Oh God, yeah.
As a multiple eight figure earner, what
was the best financial advice you ever received?
So when you partner with somebody, we call
it the call because any business is going
to need cash flow at some point.
If your partners can't make the call, when you
say, hey, we all need to put in whatever
the amount is.
If you can't make that call,
they don't need to be your partner.
But you were never afraid to
take on debt as a business owner?
Oh God, no.
Why not?
Because it was a different time.
You can't do it now.
Banks don't do that anymore.
I literally walked into a bank on Saturday
and met with the president of the bank on
the day he was off and got a
loan for $550,000 and opened my first business.
Thank you so much for your time, sir.
I appreciate you.
All right, guys.
Y'all have a great day, sir.
Thank you.
All right, you guys.
My guy's study just dropped.
Probably one of my favorite interviews I've ever done.
But guys, it all comes back to people.
Attach yourselves to great people and remember,
people will take you places that money can't.
Phenomenal interview out here in Tampa.
Let's go get this next
one and keep this video rolling.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Huh?
I've been broke before?
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
I've been broke before.
Yeah?
And what line of business are you in?
I'm in a digital marketing company.
I'm an investor.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I go all over the country just asking successful
people how they made it for the younger generation.
Could I interview you for the channel real quick?
That's dope, man.
So how long have you been an entrepreneur for?
For about three or four years, man.
Over these four years, what was the most amount
of money that you made in a single year?
It's going to be my current year.
I'm making a few million this year, bro.
Yeah.
Give me a range.
Four to five.
Four to five million dollars.
As a multiple seven-figure entrepreneur, what is
the best financial advice that you ever received?
Leverage debt.
I think a lot of people are looking to get out
of debt, which means you just come from being negative to broke.
And then another thing is if you don't learn how to leverage debt,
you'll always be working for somebody else who knows how to leverage debt.
Break that down.
How can somebody leverage debt to create wealth?
Let's just say if we leverage other people's money to
be able to buy real estate or to start a business,
now we have the capability and
opportunity to start these businesses and investments.
But we can use somebody else's
money to start something that cash flows,
and then pay back off the debt over time.
So why am I looking to pay off debt
when I can cash flow off somebody else's money
and start the things that I
want to start without my own money?
I like that concept.
You know that he's at school, right?
Yeah.
You definitely don't learn that in school.
Did you go to college?
I went to college for like
90 days, and then I dropped out.
I'm not that smart, man.
I didn't know how to
write a 10 to 15-page paper.
I kind of quit after they told
me how to write a page paper.
I'm like, ah, that ain't my thing.
How old are you now?
Yeah.
And how old were you when you became a millionaire?
Like 27.
Do you come from a lot of money?
Nah, I don't.
My father died in a car crash when
I was a kid, like one years old.
And my mom, she got taken to
jail for a few years as well.
What was the turning point to financial freedom?
One thing that I know is that
everybody do is say that stuff is hard.
Starting a business is hard.
Investing is hard.
Like getting your credit together is hard.
Well, it's hard being broke.
It's hard being in the same position
year after year after year after year.
So you got to choose what hard you want.
All right, you guys.
This video just got off to an amazing start,
and we're headed to go
get our next interview right now.
But I want to take a
quick moment to talk to you guys
about one of the greatest lessons
that I've learned in my life.
from interviewing over a thousand
millionaires in the last few years.
The greatest asset that we have as individuals
that we can never get back is our time.
That's why I want to
take a moment to talk about
the sponsor of today's video, CookUnity.
CookUnity is the first ever chef-to-consumer platform
and offers chef-prepared meals delivered right to your door,
freeing up your time to focus on growing your business
or scaling your next venture.
These meals have been a game changer for me
since I'm always traveling
the country interviewing millionaires
and building businesses at the same time.
Whenever I come back home,
instead of going to get fast food,
CookUnity has been my go-to.
And they offer incredible meals,
like grilled skirt steak with herb frites by Chris Rattel.
Or how about the chicken
shawarma rice bowl by Chase Evans
and even the oven roasted brisket rigatoni by David Aiden.
And remember this, guys, success isn't only about money.
It's about your health, taking care
of your body and your mind.
And CookUnity delivers fresh, healthy
meals crafted by top chefs,
ensuring you maintain peak
performance without sacrificing quality,
something I've seen the most successful people prioritize.
So take the leap today and invest in your health,
by going to CookUnity.com slash SOHK50
or use the link down
in the description of this video
and use my code SOHK50 for 50%
off your first order of meals at CookUnity
so you can try the meals for yourself.
But with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
I have a channel I grew to 8
million followers called the School of Hard Knocks.
We do 170 million views a month.
Can I interview you for one
minute real quick, right over here?
Thank you, my friend.
Who am I here with today?
David Bautista.
In what industry did you pursue
a career, for those that don't know?
I'm in entertainment.
I was a professional wrestler before I was an actor.
How long have you been in the entertainment business for?
Shit, man, about 25 years.
Throughout your career, what was the most amount
of money that you made in a single year?
Man, I'm not going to say, but it's to me,
it's a lot of money, but I don't want to say.
Over $10 million?
Over, yeah.
That's incredible.
Yeah.
Do you come from a lot of money?
No, I come from, you know, a
single, I was raised by a single mom.
And, you know, at times we couldn't even afford food.
I'm from kind of the worst parts of Washington,
D.C., and that's kind of how I grew up.
Until I was well into my 30s,
I didn't make any money until I was
what?
Well into my 30s.
Yeah.
What was the best advice
you ever got from a mentor?
If there's a lesson that a mentor...
As far as financial advice?
Anything, life, something that really helped
you throughout your career, your life.
Well, I mean,
there's been a few things, especially when I
was wrestling, I had a mentor named Triple H.
And there was a couple of things he
said to me that always stuck with me.
And one of the things was, you know,
when I first got there, I was so afraid.
Like, I didn't want to piss people off.
It was a hierarchy thing.
And I was so afraid of
being disrespectful or pissing somebody off.
And one day he said, Look, man,
you want to want to make money?
You want to make friends?
He said, This is a business.
You got to look at it as a business.
You're a business.
You're your own commodity.
And so I always thought
about myself as my own commodity.
I am my brand.
And so another thing he said,
he said, Just always imagine that everybody's
pointing a gun at your head.
He said, It's up to you
how many bullets you give them.
And that kind of stuck with me.
And financial advice, the best advice that I ever got,
which I always offer to,
especially to like professional athletes,
because a lot of professional athletes who
grow up, you know, not really having much.
So when you get all this money dumped
on you, you just want to buy everything
you can afford.
It's not stuff you need.
It's just stuff you want.
And the best advice
that I ever got was
actually from The Undertaker, another wrestler.
But he said it was
advice he got from his father.
He said, Always live beneath your means.
And I learned that the hard
way when I was in wrestling.
I came out of wrestling.
I literally lost everything.
I went, you know, nothing.
My house got foreclosed on.
But I had a second opportunity to
be successful with in the film industry.
And so now it's like, you
know, like every once in a year,
I'll buy something that I want, not something I need,
because I've worked really hard and
I know that I can afford it.
But I'm still believe like
I will live beneath my means.
I know I can live
more lavishly, more luxuriously, but
I will live beneath my means
because now that money in the
bank means more to me than,
you know, something that I don't really need.
Like, I don't need a Bugatti.
I'd love to have a Bugatti,
but I'm not paying three $5 million
for a car because I don't need one.
Entertainment's very competitive.
What did you do to stand out in this industry?
What did you do differently from
99% of other people in entertainment
that made you become the top 1%?
You know, you got to weed
through people and there's some there's not
you're not going to like everybody in the world.
But can you do business with
somebody like I can do business
with people I don't necessarily like?
And I understand that, you know, this is a machine.
You know, people will use me to
make money and I will use people,
not use people to make money.
But, you know, this in the entertainment industry,
like people will do business with you
if you can generate money for them.
And I will do business with them.
They can generate money for me.
So it's all a trade off.
It's got to be about who
are you willing to do business with?
And a lot of times
you're not going to like people
that you have to do business with.
Thank you, my friend. I appreciate you got amazing advice.
Guys, we just interviewed an absolute legend, Dave Batista.
He's one of the greatest WWE wrestlers
of all time. Now he's
one of the biggest Hollywood actors.
And he just gave some amazing advice,
especially when he talked about the advice
that his mentor, the legend Triple H, gave him.
He said, if you go into
business expected to be liked by everybody
and you're trying to please everybody,
you are never going to be successful.
Like Grant Cardone told me when I interviewed him,
I don't care if they like me or
they hate me as long as they call me.
Great interview with the legend Batista.
Let's go get this next one
out here in Tampa. Come on.
All right, guys, we just got to
our next destination out here in Tampa.
Eddie V's, one of the nicest
steak houses in the entire city.
My guy just pulled up in a Rolls Royce.
We're going to go see him.
What this man was able to do out here, man.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah, what's up?
Question for you. Is this your Rolls Royce?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, it's mine.
And what do you do for living out here
in Tampa to be able to afford a Rolls Royce?
I am a consultant. I'm a business consultant.
Are you an entrepreneur?
I am definitely an entrepreneur.
How long have you been a business owner for?
I've been a business owner for 37, no, 39 years.
And could I interview you real quick?
I go all over the
country just asking business owners advice
to do business.
You're an entrepreneur?
Sure.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Most amount of money I've
ever made in a single year?
$15 million.
$15 million?
Yeah.
Have you ever been broke before?
I was broke for the first part of my life.
Then I made millions of dollars.
And then I was broke again.
And now we've set it up in
such a way that that doesn't happen anymore.
What separates middle class from
wealthy people in today's world?
Poor people and middle class
people feel like everything's expensive
because they pay for everything with
money they've exchanged their time for.
And they feel like they're paying for
everything with their life because they are.
Wealthy, creative entrepreneurs like yourself, like myself,
are the ones who are going to
be the most successful entrepreneurs in the world.
We pay for things according to our creativity.
In other words, we create an
offer to pay for everything we buy.
So everything costs the same amount.
Do you believe in God?
I more than believe in God.
I trust God.
So that's, yeah, I believe
in God and I trust God.
How important has faith been for you throughout your career?
It's the most important thing in my life.
How did you build that relationship
and build that trust in God?
Maybe to speak to those people that
may not understand the importance of that
and how much that's, you know, had an impact.
So I received Christ as my
Savior when I was 16 years old.
I started reading the Bible when I was 17.
Every success principle that I learned, the very first thing
that I do is I go back and
look at Scripture and see if it lines up.
If it does, I'll follow it.
If it doesn't, I ditch it.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
I really appreciate that.
Good to meet you, young man.
Hard Knocks family, this video was incredible.
My guy, Myron, we just saw
coming out of the Rolls Royce,
just dropped a million dollars
worth of game for you guys.
But I want you guys to
like and subscribe for amazing content
we've got coming very, very soon.
And as I mentioned before,
guys, we launched an entrepreneur community,
a private entrepreneur community where
you guys can connect directly
with the multi-millionaires and the billionaires
that I interview, guys like Myron.
If you want to learn directly from them
on live calls and ask guys like him questions,
how to start and scale a business,
how to create wealth in different industries
like real estate, how to market, how to sell.
The link to join our private entrepreneur community,
the School of Mentors, is down below.
I'll see you on the inside of the community.
But with that being said,
see you in the next video.